Once the user's location preference has been stored. When do
当用户的location preference 被存储后
we make use of it? We need the preferred location on
我们什么时候该用好它呢？我们需要首选地理位置用来
we query the weather service. Luckily, in lesson 2, we
查询气象服务。幸运的是，在第二节中，我们
modified fetch weather task to accept a location parameter. We hard
修改了天气去接受地理位置参数。
coded it to be the Mountain View zip code. But
我们将它硬解码为Mountain View zip code
now we should use the location stored in shared preferences. We
但是现在我们需要使用存储在SharePreference中的地理位置
haven't explicitly shown you how to do this. So you might
我们并没有明确地向你展示如何实现，所以你可能需要
need to do some digging around. On the Ander developer site
查阅资料，可以在Android developer的网址上
to figure out how to do it. Once
弄清楚如何实现它。当你
you've made the change, check the box to continue.
完成了这个改变后，勾选这个方框并继续